<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Create a business process diagram">
<intro>
<description>This tutorial guides you through the creation of a business process diagram using BPWME editor
</description>
</intro>


<item
      skip="false"
      title="Create an empty bpwme diagram">
<description>
The first thing you will need is a bpwme diagram. If you
already have a diagram on your file system that you would like to use,
you may skip this step by clicking the &quot;Click to Skip&quot; button. If not,
select File &gt; New Diagram and give the new diagram a proper name. Then a diagram file is created automatically, with the bpwme perspective.
Notice all diagram files are
stored under the directory &quot;Documents and Settings\User\AspireRFID\IDE\BPWME\Specified Name&quot;.
</description>
</item>

<item title="Create an Open Loop Composite Business Process (OLCBProc)" skip="false">
<description>
Now you should have a BPWME editor in your workspace. The next
thing to do is creating an Open Loop Composite Business Process (OLCBProc). By default, one OLCB Process should be already existing in the editor with the given name. If not, select 
OLCBProc on the right side of the editor palette, move the mouse cursor to the 
editing area and left click on the mouse. You can see an OLCB Process is created. 
You can edit the id and name in the properties view.
</description>
</item>
<item title="Create a Close Loop Composite Business Process (CLCBProc)">
<description>
You can create a Close Loop Composite Business Process (CLCBProc) by choosing 
   CLCBProc on the right side of the editor palette, just like creating an OLCBProc. 
   Notice CLCBProc can only be putted inside OLCBProc.
</description>
</item>
<item
      title="Create an Elementary Business Process (EBProc)">
   <description>
      You can create an Elementary Business Process (EBProc) by choosing 
      EBProc on the right side of the editor palette, just like creating an 
      OLCBProc. Notice EBProc can only be putted inside CLCBProc.
   </description>
</item>
<item
      title="Edit Master Data">
   <description>
      <b>Body</b>
   </description>
</item>
<item
      title="Edit ECSpec and LRSpec">
   <description>
      <b>Body</b>
   </description>
</item>
<item
      title="XML Editor">
   <description>
      <b>Body</b>
   </description>
</item>
</cheatsheet>
