<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Library model tutorial">
<intro>
<description>This tutorial guides you through the creation of a simple Java
model with three Java classes.
</description>
</intro>
<item title="Open the Java Perspective">
<description>Select Window > Open Perspective > Java in the menubar at the
top of the workbench. This step changes the perspective to set up the
Eclipse workbench for Java development.
</description>
</item>
<item title="Create a Java project" skip="true">
<description>The first thing you will need is a Java Project. If you
already have a Java project in your workspace that you would like to use,
you may skip this step by clicking the "Click to Skip" button. If not,
select File > New > Project... and choose Java Project in the list.
Complete the subsequent pages as required.
</description>
</item>
<item title="Create a Java package" skip="true">
<description>You should now have a Java project in your workspace. The next
thing to do is creating a package. Use the Eclipse tools by selecting
File  > New  > Package action. Give the package a name for example
"tutorial.library.model" and click the "Finish" button. If you already
have a project with a package you might as well skip this step.
</description>
</item>
<item title="Create the library model classes">
<description>Now you should be set up for creating your library model. The
library model consists of three Java classes, a library class, a writer
class and a book class. Use the Java class wizard by selecting
File  > New > Class. Repeat this for every class.
</description>
</item>
<item title="Package your classes into an archive">
<description>In the last step of this tutorial you will package the created
classes into a Java archive or JAR file. Therefore, right-click your Java
project and select the "Export..." action. In the wizard select "JAR file"
and click the "Next" button. On the next page specify a location and name
for the JAR file and click "Finish". You have now successfully created a
little Java model and packaged that into a JAR file.
</description>
</item>
</cheatsheet>